this is how
we think that
innovation is going
to play out
in the equity
markets, the market
cap. On the
right-hand side
there, you can
see what happened
to railroad stocks
as a percent
of the
total global equity
market cap, 65%.
You can see
where we are
now, and we
think this revolution
is even
bigger, as
I mentioned.
And really just
starting in its
first few
years at least.
And you can
see where we
think innovation's going
to go as
a percent of
global market cap.
Again, we've
just begun.
We don't think
AI hype is
where we
are at all.
We do not
think we're in
the equivalent of
the tech and
telecom bubble.
We're very
happy that many
people are worried
about it.